LUKE BAILEY

Location: Melbourne, Victoria **Email**: lukejbailey2014@gmail.com

Portfolio: whiskerz1337.github.io/Portfolio

ABOUT ME

I'm a friendly, focused, and inquisitive Cybersecurity Student with a passion for software development. I work well both alone and as part of a team, and thoroughly enjoy problem solving both in the workplace and in my free time.

On a more personal level, I love gaming, I speak Spanish as a second language, and have been a self-taught guitarist for over 20 years.

TECHNICAL SKILLS SUMMARY

Operating Systems: Linux, Windows CLIs: Unix, Windows, Cisco IOS

Languages: JavaScript, Python, Bash, Rust Web Development: React, Node.js

Dev Ops: Git, GitHub, Docker, Debian **Pen Testing**: Kali, Metasploit, netcat

Cybersecurity: Incident Response, Risk Assessments, Vulnerability Scanning Communication, Pair Programming

EDUCATION

Advanced CertificateCybersecurityAugust 2022 - PresentCert IVCybersecurityAugust 2021 - June 2022BSc (Hons) 2.2Music Technology2010 - 2014

EMPLOYMENT

1800GJ February 2020 - Present

Truck team Member

Direct Line Group January 2019 – December 2019

EVO consultant

Direct Line Group January 2017 – December 2018

Landlord & Tradesmen Consultant